incruises.com 2019-11-01

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                                                                         P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
      I.          Acceptance of Terms
      This Privacy Policy describes INCRUISES’ policies and procedures on the collection, use and
      disclosure of your information.          INCRUISES (“INCRUISES INTERNATIONAL LLC”,
      “INCRUISES”, INCRUISES LLC, INCRUISES EUROPE SLU, INDALO CRUISES SL,
      “INCRUISES.com”, “The Company”). Hereinafter referred to as "we", "us", "our" or “INCRUISES”,
      receives your information through our various web sites, SMS, APIs, services and third-parties
      (hereinafter referred to as the "Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the
      collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in
      this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your
      information may be used by INCRUISES in the United States or any other country where INCRUISES
      operates. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the INCRUISES Terms of
      Service. Each time you use the Services, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to be
      bound by the Terms of Service. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you must
      discontinue using the Services and terminate your membership.
      II.         Information Collection and Use
      Visitors of the website may view various web pages without providing any personal information. If
      you desire to have the INCRUISES provide services or goods to you or an organization of which you
      have representative capacity, INCRUISES may ask you to provide certain information about yourself or
      your organization by filling out and submitting one or more forms. Providing personal information is
      optional, but INCRUISES reserves the right to refuse service to you if you are unable or unwilling to
      provide certain requested personal information as determined by INCRUISES.
      The personal information that you provide in connection with the use of the website or the products
      and/or services provided by INCRUISES is protected in numerous ways. Access to your personal
      information collected during the purchasing of a product or service is available through a password and
      unique user ID. The password is encrypted. INCRUISES recommends that you do not divulge your
      password to anyone. In addition, your personal information resides on secure servers that only selected
      personnel and contractors have access to via password. INCRUISES encrypts your personal
      information as it is transferred to the Company and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                        REF: DEC-2018                                           Page 1

                                                                                          P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
      viewing such information.
      INCRUISES collects your information in order to record, support and facilitate your use of the website
      and to prevent fraud and unlawful use. If you purchase or register for products and/or services, the
      personal information may be used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits
      that may be made available to users. Your personal information may also be used to track your
      preferences in order to provide an experience customized to your tastes, or to contact you in regards to
      changes to the site that may affect your account or to update you as to new or updated features.
      INCRUISES does not share personal information it receives from residents of California or from
      residents of any other place with such other organizations for marketing purposes unless we have
      received an opt-in from you. If you were referred to our services by an Independent Business Partner,
      your contact information (name, address, email address, and/or telephone number) will be shared with
      the Independent Business Partner who referred you.
      III.        Information Collected Upon Registration
      When you create or reconfigure a INCRUISES account, you provide some personal information, such
      as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your
      name and username may be listed publicly on our Services. Without your permission, we will not
      share, rent or sell any of this registration information to any third party in any other way than is (i)
      disclosed by this privacy policy or (ii) required by applicable law, regulation or court order.
      IV.         Additional Information
      You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, your
      location, or a picture. You may customize your account with information such as a cell phone number.
      Without your permission, we will not share, rent or sell any of this registration information to any third
      party in any other way than is (i) disclosed by this privacy policy or (ii) required by applicable law,
      regulation or court order.
      V.          Log Data
      In order to reduce errors in our database(s), authenticate our users, prevent fraud and prevent abuse of
      INCRUISES’ web site and/or the product and services INCRUISES provides, as well as to provide
      more consistent, relevant experiences to INCRUISES’ users, INCRUISES may on occasion
      supplement or correct the personal information you submit to INCRUISES and your Internet Protocol
      (IP) address with information in our other databases or information from third-party sources. As
      permissible, INCRUISES may also supplement the personal information you provide to INCRUISES
      with demographic and other information stored in third-party databases in order to make it more likely
      that communications INCRUISES may send will be of interest to you.
      VI.         Links
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                                                                                 Page 2

                                                                                           P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
       INCRUISES may keep track of how you interact with links in posts and emails by redirecting clicks or
       through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to
       share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.
       Our services may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that INCRUISES is not responsible for
       the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and
       to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects Personal Information. This
       privacy statement applies solely to information collected by INCRUISES websites.
       VII.       Cookies
       Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to
       improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching
       and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your
       computer's hard disk. INCRUISES may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better
       understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic
       routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept
       cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt
       you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.
       VIII. Third Party Services
       INCRUISES uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services and to help
       us understand the use of our Services. These services may collect information sent by your browser as
       part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.
       IX.        Information Sharing and Disclosure
       INCRUISES recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on
       the website and in connection with the products and services provided by INCRUISES. INCRUISES
       will respect your legal rights regarding access to, and correction and deletion of, your personal
       information. INCRUISES may communicate information to you regarding products, services, and
       special offers available from INCRUISES unless you have opted not to receive such communications
       or such communications are prohibited by law, although in such cases INCRUISES may find it
       necessary to continue to communicate with you regarding your use of the website and the products and
       services. In addition, you may receive communications and special offers from selected third party
       providers, but only if you previously opted in to receive such communications. INCRUISES will not
       provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent. If you have opted to
       receive email communications from our selected third party providers and later wish to discontinue
       receipt of these emails, please contact those third parties directly to update your preferences.
       X.         Service Providers
       We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                                                                                Page 3

                                                                                          P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
      your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these
      functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this
      privacy policy. We may provide products and/or services that may require you to accept one or more
      privacy policies of third party providers. It is your duty to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies
      of the third party providers. If you do not accept the privacy policy of the third party providers,
      INCRUISES reserves the right to refuse services to you.
      XI.         Independent Business Partner Program
      If you sign up under the INCRUISES Independent Business Partner Program, you will be required to
      read and agree to the terms of the INCRUISES Independent Business Partner Program Agreement
      before being allowed to receive compensation for referring anyone to the Site. Please read the terms
      carefully before agreeing to participate in the Independent Business Partner Program. We will use the
      email address that you provide to us to contact you regarding the enrollment in the Independent
      Business Partner Program, and we will use the address that you provide to us to send you any payments
      owed to you under the terms of the Independent Business Partner Program or any other system
      available to us that will facilitate the transfer of these funds. If you were referred to the Independent
      Business Partner Program by another Independent Business Partner, your contact information (name,
      address, email address, and/or telephone number) will be shared with the Independent Business Partner
      who referred you.
      XII.        Online Surveys and Contests
      INCRUISES may conduct, on occasion, a survey to collect information about your preferences and the
      preferences of other users. These surveys are optional and your responses will be kept anonymous.
      INCRUISES may also offer contests to qualifying users. In order to participate, we may ask for your
      contact and demographic information such as your name, your email address and your mailing address.
      Except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy, none of the information you provide in relation
      to a contest is shared with third parties, except in summary form, if at all. The demographic information
      that INCRUISES collects in the registration process and through surveys and contests is utilized to help
      us improve our Services. This may include targeting advertising to you about our Services. Information
      we gather through a contest may also be disclosed to third parties as necessary for prize fulfillment and
      for other aspects of any contest or similar offering.
      XIII. The INCRUISES Payment System
      The INCRUISES Payment Service allows a user to pay with a credit card, wire transfer, ACH, debit
      card or check. INCRUISES will collect your payment information and/or other entered financial
      institution information such as bank account numbers and will use that information to bill you for
      membership fees and/or to perform a payment on behalf of a third party provider. INCRUISES may
      use and disclose such payment information and/or other entered financial institution information to
      third parties as necessary to complete such billing operation.
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                                                                                  Page 4

                                                                                           P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
       Please see our Payment Agreement for more information on payments.
       XIV. Email to Friends Feature
       INCRUISES lets you send invitations to join the Site to friends, family and other personal connections
       (hereinafter referred to as "Friends") via email and social media posts. INCRUISES also offers the
       ability to send Friends emails about the Services provided by INCRUISES. If you choose to use these
       features, you may be assured that INCRUISES will only use your Friends' email addresses to notify
       them of the Services and Business Opportunities available on the Site. INCRUISES will not share your
       Friend’s emails and information with any third party providers or advertisers in any way; except (i) for
       the purposes of sending the invitations to join our site if you choose to use this feature (ii) as otherwise
       may be provided for in this agreement.
       XV.        Law and Harm
       We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law,
       regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical
       issues; or to protect INCRUISES’ rights or property.
       XVI. Business Transfers
       In the event that INCRUISES is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of
       assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this
       privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.
       XVII. Non-Private or Non-Personal Information
       The Company may collect information about the use of the web site and the third party software
       packages listed therein, such as the number of downloads, services purchased/utilized, how many users
       visit the website daily, web pages visited, and the IP address of your computer. This information is
       generally collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually, although IP address
       and Session ID in relation to purchases may be tracked as part of the Company's customer order review
       and fraud prevention efforts.
       The Company may use aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for improving the website and the
       products and services provided by the Company.
       XVIII.Modifying Your Personal Information
       If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify some of the
       personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.
       Certain personal information not accessible online by you (e.g., IP address) that you provide is
       accessible only by selected personnel and contractors via password and is not modifiable by you.
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                                                                                   Page 5

                                                                                      P R I VA C Y P O L I C Y
       XIX. Our Policy Towards Children
       Our Services are not directed to people under 18. If you become aware that your child has provided us
       with personal information without your consent, please contact us. We do not knowingly collect
       personal information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided
       us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's
       account.
        XX.       Changes to Our Privacy Policy
       From time to time INCRUISES may update this Privacy Policy when our information practices are
       modified or changed. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will announce that this policy
       has been changed at our website home page for a period of 30 days. Your continued use of the Services
       after we post a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement
       to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes in the revised Privacy Policy. If you object to
       any such changes, you must cease using the Services. We therefore encourage you to periodically
       review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
       XXI. Questions
       Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to support@incruises.com
       XXII. Effective Date
       The effective date of this Privacy Policy is September 1st, 2015.
NCRUISES®. All Rights Reserved                                                                              Page 6
